<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Homes on</title><link>https://f12.biz/home/</link><description>Recent content in Homes on</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://f12.biz/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Home</title><link>https://f12.biz/home/home/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://f12.biz/home/home/</guid><description>&lt;section id="about" class="section rad-animation-group pb-0">
 &lt;div class="rad-fade-down">
 &lt;div class="row d-flex flex-column-reverse flex-md-row">
 &lt;div class="about__profile-picture col-12 col-md-6">
 










 
 



 
 


 &lt;picture class="">
 
 

 &lt;source srcset="https://f12.biz/images/about/user-picture_hu_c3b7b6ea83b51435.webp 1x, https://f12.biz/images/about/user-picture_hu_d7801b9edf4dc93e.webp 2x" type="image/webp" />
 &lt;source srcset="https://f12.biz/images/about/user-picture_hu_37558d2316509883.png 1x, https://f12.biz/images/about/user-picture_hu_cf527af17c9c9268.png 2x" type="image/png">

 &lt;img
 width="561"
 height="535"
 class="lozad img-responsive image-left-overflow"
 data-src="https://f12.biz/images/about/user-picture_hu_37558d2316509883.png"
 alt=''
 src="data:image/gif;base64,R0lGODlhBwACAIAAAP///wAAACH5BAEAAAEALAAAAAAHAAIAAAIDjI9YADs="
 loading="lazy"
 decoding="async"
 />
 &lt;/picture>

 &lt;/div>
 &lt;div class="col-12 col-md-6 my-auto">
 &lt;h1>Who am I?&lt;/h1>
 &lt;div class="about-me content lead">
 &lt;/br>&lt;/br>Based in Valencia, California US, I specialize in IT infrastructure, support, and cloud operations—helping organizations scale with reliability and security. Most recently, I led the full technical integration of Praedicat into Moody’s, overseeing system migrations, decommissions, and compliance alignment. With a hands-on approach and a focus on clarity, automation, and cross-team collaboration, I bring over 15 years of experience across enterprise IT, security, and user support. I'm passionate about building systems that are stable, secure, and built to last—while fostering collaboration between people, processes, and platforms.
 &lt;/div>
 
 &lt;/div>
 &lt;/div>
 &lt;/div>
&lt;/section>




&lt;div class="container">
 &lt;div class="row platform-links shortcode">
 &lt;div class="col-12">
	
	 
	&lt;a
	 href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/denistolochko/"
	 target="_blank"
	 rel="noopener noreferrer"
	 aria-label="linkedin"
	 >&lt;i class="icon-linkedin">&lt;/i>
	&lt;/a>

	
	 
	&lt;a
	 href="https://github.com/akajedi"
	 target="_blank"
	 rel="noopener noreferrer"
	 aria-label="square-github"
	 >&lt;i class="icon-square-github">&lt;/i>
	&lt;/a>

&lt;/div>
 &lt;/div>
&lt;/div>





&lt;section
 id="education"
 class="section section--border-bottom rad-animation-group"
>
 &lt;div class="container-education">
 &lt;div class="row rad-fade-down">
 &lt;div class="col-12">
 &lt;h2>Education&lt;/h2>
 &lt;div class="row pt-2 pt-md-4">
 
 &lt;div class="col-12 col-sm-6 mb-4 mb-sm-0">
 &lt;div class="education">
 &lt;div class="education__date">1996-2000&lt;/div>
 &lt;div class="education__title">Yurga Technical College of Industry and Law&lt;/div>
 &lt;div class="education__degree">Technician in CNC Programming (Computer Numerical Control)&lt;/div>
 &lt;/div>
 &lt;/div>
 
 &lt;div class="col-12 col-sm-6 mb-4 mb-sm-0">
 &lt;div class="education">
 &lt;div class="education__date">2000-2006&lt;/div>
 &lt;div class="education__title">Tomsk State University&lt;/div>
 &lt;div class="education__degree">Law Degree, specialization in Jurisprudence. Graduation thesis: The Sales Contract in Civil Law.&lt;/div>
 &lt;/div>
 &lt;/div>
 
 &lt;/div>
 &lt;/div>
 &lt;/div>
 &lt;/div>
&lt;/section>








 
 
 


&lt;section id="experience-single" class="section-experience section section--border-bottom rad-animation-group flex-grow-1">
 &lt;div class="row flex-column-reverse flex-md-row rad-fade-down">
 &lt;div class="experience-list col-12 col-md-6">
 &lt;h2>
 
 Experience
 
 &lt;/h2>

 
 

 

 

 

 
 &lt;div class="experience">
 &lt;a href="https://f12.biz/experience/job-5/" class="experience__link">
 &lt;div class="experience__header">
 
 
 &lt;div class="experience__meta">
 &lt;div class="experience__date">Oct 2024- Jul 2025&lt;/div>
 &lt;div class="experience__title">Sr. Technical Support Analyst&lt;/div>
 &lt;div class="experience__company">
 Moody&amp;#39;s, Inc.
 &lt;span class="experience__location">Culver City, California&lt;/span>
 &lt;/div>
 &lt;/div>
 &lt;div class="experience__description d-none d-print-block">
 &lt;h1>Sr. Technical Support Analyst&lt;/h1>
 As the sole in-house IT administrator at Praedicat, I was fully responsible for managing and maintaining the company&amp;rsquo;s IT infrastructure across multiple locations. My role combined hands-on technical support with long-term infrastructure planning, ensuring system reliability, security, and scalability for a growing organization.
I led the procurement, deployment, and lifecycle management of hardware, including desktops, laptops, servers, and network equipment. I managed inventory, vendor coordination, and internal asset tracking while supporting all staff with technical troubleshooting and end-user support across macOS, Windows, and Linux systems.
I maintained the company&amp;rsquo;s internal network, file sharing, backup systems, remote access, and account provisioning, while also documenting system configurations, network topology, and shared resources. This documentation supported business continuity, onboarding, and security audits.
Security and operational efficiency were priorities. I implemented best practices in access control, system patching, endpoint protection, and secure backups. I regularly reviewed systems to identify risks and worked proactively to reduce vulnerabilities. I also used Python scripting to automate tasks, streamline reporting, and eliminate repetitive manual work.
Key contributions:
Independently managed all IT operations for a cloud-integrated startup environment
Procured and supported all end-user and infrastructure hardware
Resolved internal support issues across teams with minimal downtime
Maintained detailed documentation of IT systems and processes
Developed automation scripts to increase efficiency and reliability
This role established my expertise in technical operations, infrastructure support, system security, and cross-functional collaboration — all of which I carried into the Moody’s acquisition project.

 &lt;/div>
 &lt;/div>
 &lt;/a>
 &lt;/div>
 
 &lt;div class="experience">
 &lt;a href="https://f12.biz/experience/job-4/" class="experience__link">
 &lt;div class="experience__header">
 
 
 &lt;div class="experience__meta">
 &lt;div class="experience__date">Nov 2018- Oct 2024&lt;/div>
 &lt;div class="experience__title">Sr. System Administrator &amp;amp; IT Engineer&lt;/div>
 &lt;div class="experience__company">
 Praedicat, Inc.
 &lt;span class="experience__location">Culver City, California&lt;/span>
 &lt;/div>
 &lt;/div>
 &lt;div class="experience__description d-none d-print-block">
 &lt;h1>&lt;/h1>
 As the sole in-house IT administrator at Praedicat, I was fully responsible for managing and maintaining the company&amp;rsquo;s IT infrastructure across multiple locations. My role combined hands-on technical support with long-term infrastructure planning, ensuring system reliability, security, and scalability for a growing organization.
I led the procurement, deployment, and lifecycle management of hardware, including desktops, laptops, servers, and network equipment. I managed inventory, vendor coordination, and internal asset tracking while supporting all staff with technical troubleshooting and end-user support across macOS, Windows, and Linux systems.
I maintained the company&amp;rsquo;s internal network, file sharing, backup systems, remote access, and account provisioning, while also documenting system configurations, network topology, and shared resources. This documentation supported business continuity, onboarding, and security audits.
Security and operational efficiency were priorities. I implemented best practices in access control, system patching, endpoint protection, and secure backups. I regularly reviewed systems to identify risks and worked proactively to reduce vulnerabilities. I also used Python scripting to automate tasks, streamline reporting, and eliminate repetitive manual work.
Key contributions:
Independently managed all IT operations for a cloud-integrated startup environment
Procured and supported all end-user and infrastructure hardware
Resolved internal support issues across teams with minimal downtime
Maintained detailed documentation of IT systems and processes
Developed automation scripts to increase efficiency and reliability
This role established my expertise in technical operations, infrastructure support, system security, and cross-functional collaboration — all of which I carried into the Moody’s acquisition project.

 &lt;/div>
 &lt;/div>
 &lt;/a>
 &lt;/div>
 
 &lt;div class="experience">
 &lt;a href="https://f12.biz/experience/job-3/" class="experience__link">
 &lt;div class="experience__header">
 
 
 &lt;div class="experience__meta">
 &lt;div class="experience__date">Jun 2017- Jun 2018&lt;/div>
 &lt;div class="experience__title">IT Engineer&lt;/div>
 &lt;div class="experience__company">
 T3Leads .
 &lt;span class="experience__location">Burbank, California&lt;/span>
 &lt;/div>
 &lt;/div>
 &lt;div class="experience__description d-none d-print-block">
 &lt;h1>&lt;/h1>
 I served as a Senior Systems Administrator and Network Security Administrator. I was responsible for securing and maintaining a high-traffic infrastructure across multiple regions. My role involved leading internal security audits, working closely with white-hat teams for penetration testing, and deploying monitoring tools to ensure real-time visibility and threat detection. I coordinated system patching, managed disaster recovery plans, and maintained reliable backups for operational resilience. Additionally, I resolved complex network issues, deployed antivirus and asset management agents across environments, and ensured all systems met security and compliance standards. My work directly supported the stability and scalability of a distributed infrastructure serving thousands of affiliates worldwide

 &lt;/div>
 &lt;/div>
 &lt;/a>
 &lt;/div>
 
 &lt;div class="experience">
 &lt;a href="https://f12.biz/experience/job-2/" class="experience__link">
 &lt;div class="experience__header">
 
 
 &lt;div class="experience__meta">
 &lt;div class="experience__date">May 2012- June 2017&lt;/div>
 &lt;div class="experience__title">Systems Administrator&lt;/div>
 &lt;div class="experience__company">
 T3Leads .
 &lt;span class="experience__location">Encino, California&lt;/span>
 &lt;/div>
 &lt;/div>
 &lt;div class="experience__description d-none d-print-block">
 &lt;h1>&lt;/h1>
 T3Leads is the world’s premier online lead generation firm and affiliate network. T3Leads’ expertise is in providing quality payday loan leads, as the go-to pay-per-lead affiliate network for the financial sector. With over 10,000 active affiliates, T3Leads currently operates in the US, UK, Canada, and Australia.
As a Senior Systems Administrator &amp;amp; Network Security Administrator at T3Leads, my responsibilities include: Network Security • Ensuring system security, spearheading security audits, and working with the Hi Level White Hackers team for penetration testing • Utilizing security tools to monitor the networks and reporting and responding immediately to security or usability issues and incidents • Writing custom monitoring plugins to ensure system security • Coordinating and installing patches and releases on web applications and development, pre production, and production systems • Diagnosing and resolving network connectivity interruptions, including malware infections, faulty hardware, and configuration issues • Implementing functional backup plans and disaster recovery plans • Scheduling, creating, and verifying backups on a regular and ad hoc basis • Deploying backup, antivirus, monitoring, blade logic, and asset management agents as servers are added into the network • Hands on experience with computer forensics, penetration and vulnerability testing tools, and conducting internal audits, vulnerability scanning, firewall, penetration testing • Install, diagnose, repair, and upgrade all hardware, applications and equipment, including regulation of any software incidents

 &lt;/div>
 &lt;/div>
 &lt;/a>
 &lt;/div>
 
 &lt;div class="experience">
 &lt;a href="https://f12.biz/experience/job-1/" class="experience__link">
 &lt;div class="experience__header">
 
 
 &lt;div class="experience__meta">
 &lt;div class="experience__date">Oct 2011 - May 2012&lt;/div>
 &lt;div class="experience__title">Software Engineer&lt;/div>
 &lt;div class="experience__company">
 T3Leads .
 &lt;span class="experience__location">Encino, California&lt;/span>
 &lt;/div>
 &lt;/div>
 &lt;div class="experience__description d-none d-print-block">
 &lt;h1>&lt;/h1>
 T3Leads, the leading provider of online lead generation and affiliate network services, specializes in delivering top-notch payday loan leads to the financial industry. With a thriving network of over 10,000 active affiliates, the company operates globally, serving clients in the US, UK, Canada, and Australia.
As a PHP Developer at T3Leads, I was responsible for using a variety of technologies to create websites and web applications, and developing user-friendly front- and back-end interfaces using HTML, PHP, CSS, and JavaScript. I was able to work independently with minimal supervision, maintaining a close working relationship with the Executive team.
I demonstrated a high level of technical skill, as well as strong interpersonal abilities, allowing me to effectively manage multiple tasks in a fast-paced, dynamic environment.

 &lt;/div>
 &lt;/div>
 &lt;/a>
 &lt;/div>
 

 
 &lt;/div>
 &lt;div class="experience-description col-12 col-md-6">
 
 









&lt;div class="container-experience">
 &lt;div class="row">
 &lt;h2> &lt;/h2>
 &lt;div class="lead">&lt;/br>&lt;/br>&lt;/br>&lt;/br>&lt;/br>Over the course of my career, I’ve built a strong foundation in IT operations, system administration, infrastructure support, and cloud integration. I’ve contributed to organizations of various sizes — from fast-paced tech firms to global enterprises — where I’ve led high-impact transitions, maintained business-critical systems, and supported cross-functional teams across multiple platforms and time zones. My experience reflects a hands-on, solutions-focused approach, with a consistent commitment to reliability, security, and operational efficiency.&lt;/div>
 &lt;/div>

 &lt;div class="row">
 
 &lt;div class="col-12 col-lg-4">
 &lt;a
 href='https://www.linkedin.com/in/adrianmoreno/'
 class="btn btn-primary btn-block w-100"
 target="_blank"
 rel="noopener noreferrer"
 >
 
 LinkedIn
 &lt;i class="icon-arrow-right">&lt;/i>
 &lt;/a>
 &lt;/div>
 

 
 &lt;div class="col-12 col-lg-4">
 &lt;a
 href='https://f12.biz/img/general/user-smile-fill.svg'
 class="btn btn-frameless w-100"
 target="_blank"
 rel="noopener noreferrer"
 >
 
 Download resume
 &lt;/a>
 &lt;/div>
 

 
 &lt;div class="col-12 col-lg-4">
 &lt;a
 href='https://f12.biz/experience'
 class="btn btn-frameless w-100"
 rel="noopener noreferrer"
 >
 
 View all
 &lt;/a>
 &lt;/div>
 
 &lt;/div>
&lt;/div>

 &lt;/div>
 &lt;/div>
&lt;/section>






&lt;section id="testimonial" class="section rad-animation-group section--border-bottom">
 &lt;div class="container">
 
 &lt;h2 class="rad-fade-down">Colleague Feedback&lt;/h2>
 &lt;div class="row row--padded mb-0 rad-fade-down">
 
 &lt;div class="col-12 col-md-4 mb-5 mb-md-0 testimonial container">
 &lt;i class="icon-quote-left">&lt;/i>
 &lt;p>I echo everything Stephen C. Jones has said about Denis, he was a great team member and immensely helped me. Good luck Denis 💪&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>