<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>My Expirience on</title><link>https://akajedi.github.io/experience/</link><description>Recent content in My Expirience on</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://akajedi.github.io/experience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sr. Technical Support Analyst</title><link>https://akajedi.github.io/experience/job-5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://akajedi.github.io/experience/job-5/</guid><description>&lt;p>As the sole in-house IT administrator at Praedicat, I was fully responsible for managing and maintaining the company&amp;rsquo;s IT infrastructure across multiple locations. My role combined hands-on technical support with long-term infrastructure planning, ensuring system reliability, security, and scalability for a growing organization.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I led the procurement, deployment, and lifecycle management of hardware, including desktops, laptops, servers, and network equipment. I managed inventory, vendor coordination, and internal asset tracking while supporting all staff with technical troubleshooting and end-user support across macOS, Windows, and Linux systems.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Puesto #3</title><link>https://akajedi.github.io/experience/job-3.es/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://akajedi.github.io/experience/job-3.es/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="3rd-job-gerente-general">3rd job: Gerente General&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Con una traducción al español, se puede llegar a cualquier parte.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title/><link>https://akajedi.github.io/experience/job-4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://akajedi.github.io/experience/job-4/</guid><description>&lt;p>As the sole in-house IT administrator at Praedicat, I was fully responsible for managing and maintaining the company&amp;rsquo;s IT infrastructure across multiple locations. My role combined hands-on technical support with long-term infrastructure planning, ensuring system reliability, security, and scalability for a growing organization.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I led the procurement, deployment, and lifecycle management of hardware, including desktops, laptops, servers, and network equipment. I managed inventory, vendor coordination, and internal asset tracking while supporting all staff with technical troubleshooting and end-user support across macOS, Windows, and Linux systems.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Poste #3</title><link>https://akajedi.github.io/experience/job-3.fr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://akajedi.github.io/experience/job-3.fr/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="réparer-le-monde-un-octet-à-la-fois">Réparer le monde, un octet à la fois&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Prise de contrôle hostile - qui est le patron maintenant !&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Poste #2</title><link>https://akajedi.github.io/experience/job-2.fr/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://akajedi.github.io/experience/job-2.fr/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="réparer-le-monde-un-octet-à-la-fois">Réparer le monde, un octet à la fois&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Poursuivant la quête.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Trabajo #2</title><link>https://akajedi.github.io/experience/job-2.es/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://akajedi.github.io/experience/job-2.es/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="arreglando-el-mundo-un-byte-a-la-vez">Arreglando el mundo, un byte a la vez&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Continuando la misión.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Trabajo #1</title><link>https://akajedi.github.io/experience/job-1.es/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://akajedi.github.io/experience/job-1.es/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="arreglando-el-mundo-un-byte-a-la-vez">Arreglando el mundo, un byte a la vez&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>El comienzo de una gran carrera.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title/><link>https://akajedi.github.io/experience/job-3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://akajedi.github.io/experience/job-3/</guid><description>&lt;p>I served as a Senior Systems Administrator and Network Security Administrator. I was responsible for securing and maintaining a high-traffic infrastructure across multiple regions. My role involved leading internal security audits, working closely with white-hat teams for penetration testing, and deploying monitoring tools to ensure real-time visibility and threat detection. I coordinated system patching, managed disaster recovery plans, and maintained reliable backups for operational resilience. Additionally, I resolved complex network issues, deployed antivirus and asset management agents across environments, and ensured all systems met security and compliance standards. My work directly supported the stability and scalability of a distributed infrastructure serving thousands of affiliates worldwide&lt;/p></description></item><item><title/><link>https://akajedi.github.io/experience/job-2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://akajedi.github.io/experience/job-2/</guid><description>&lt;p>T3Leads is the world’s premier online lead generation firm and affiliate network. T3Leads’ expertise is in providing quality payday loan leads, as the go-to pay-per-lead affiliate network for the financial sector. With over 10,000 active affiliates, T3Leads currently operates in the US, UK, Canada, and Australia.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As a Senior Systems Administrator &amp;amp; Network Security Administrator at T3Leads, my responsibilities include: Network Security
• Ensuring system security, spearheading security audits, and working with the Hi Level White Hackers team for penetration testing
• Utilizing security tools to monitor the networks and reporting and responding immediately to security or usability issues and incidents
• Writing custom monitoring plugins to ensure system security
• Coordinating and installing patches and releases on web applications and development, pre production, and production systems
• Diagnosing and resolving network connectivity interruptions, including malware infections, faulty hardware, and configuration issues
• Implementing functional backup plans and disaster recovery plans
• Scheduling, creating, and verifying backups on a regular and ad hoc basis
• Deploying backup, antivirus, monitoring, blade logic, and asset management agents as servers are added into the network
• Hands on experience with computer forensics, penetration and vulnerability testing tools, and conducting internal audits, vulnerability scanning, firewall, penetration testing
• Install, diagnose, repair, and upgrade all hardware, applications and equipment, including regulation of any software incidents&lt;/p></description></item><item><title/><link>https://akajedi.github.io/experience/job-1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://akajedi.github.io/experience/job-1/</guid><description>&lt;p>T3Leads, the leading provider of online lead generation and affiliate network services, specializes in delivering top-notch payday loan leads to the financial industry. With a thriving network of over 10,000 active affiliates, the company operates globally, serving clients in the US, UK, Canada, and Australia.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As a PHP Developer at T3Leads, I was responsible for using a variety of technologies to create websites and web applications, and developing user-friendly front- and back-end interfaces using HTML, PHP, CSS, and JavaScript. I was able to work independently with minimal supervision, maintaining a close working relationship with the Executive team.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Expérience</title><link>https://akajedi.github.io/experience/_index.fr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://akajedi.github.io/experience/_index.fr/</guid><description>&lt;p>C&amp;rsquo;est ici que vous pouvez mettre en avant un peu de votre expérience. Années d&amp;rsquo;expérience totale, spécialisation, etc.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Le contenu de cette introduction provient du fichier &lt;code>content/experience/_index.md&lt;/code>.
Ce type de contenu, les &amp;ldquo;pages d&amp;rsquo;index&amp;rdquo;, sont appelées &amp;ldquo;branch bundles&amp;rdquo; (paquets de branche). Vous pouvez en savoir plus sur &lt;a href="https://gohugo.io/content-management/sections/#template-selection">&lt;strong>les sections et les paquets&lt;/strong> dans la documentation de Hugo&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Le contenu pour chaque élément d&amp;rsquo;expérience (sur lesquels vous pouvez cliquer à gauche) est défini dans le dossier &lt;code>content/experience&lt;/code>, avec un élément de contenu par expérience, comme dans &lt;code>job-1.fr.md&lt;/code>, &lt;code>job-2.fr.md&lt;/code>, etc.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Experiencia</title><link>https://akajedi.github.io/experience/_index.es/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://akajedi.github.io/experience/_index.es/</guid><description>&lt;p>Aquí es donde puedes destacar un poco sobre tu experiencia. Años de experiencia total, especialización, etc.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>El contenido en esta introducción viene del archivo &lt;code>content/experience/_index.md&lt;/code>.
Este tipo de contenido, las &amp;ldquo;páginas índice&amp;rdquo;, se denominan &amp;ldquo;branch bundles&amp;rdquo; (paquetes de rama). Puede leer más sobre &lt;a href="https://gohugo.io/content-management/sections/#template-selection">&lt;strong>secciones y paquetes&lt;/strong> en la documentación de Hugo&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>El contenido para cada elemento de experiencia (en los que puedes hacer clic a la izquierda) se define en la carpeta &lt;code>content/experience&lt;/code>, con un elemento de contenido por experiencia, como en &lt;code>job-1.es.md&lt;/code>, &lt;code>job-2.es.md&lt;/code>, etc.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>